No living creature was
harmed during the filming.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
The dogs of the one that set this trap.
Come with your all.
I will not leave any of you alive.
Come. Come to me.
Mother! Hold on, mother!
Bala!
I'll kill you now!
Come. Come!
It's the end of the road for you, Bala!
Where did these people come?!
Mother, hold on. Please.
Mother, no.
No, please, hang on!
No. No!
You laugh like a hyena
that has seen a lion.
Come.
Come with your all!
-We're here, Osman Bey!
-We're here to help, my Bey!
Lions!
-I know where they are.
-Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
This way.
Come on, quickly.
Hurry up.
How great!
Thank Allah, mother! Mother?
Mother! No! Malhun!
Bala!
Soldiers! We are withdrawing!
Who are you? Take off your covers!
It's obvious that you are on
the right side.
Mother! Mother!
Mother! Wake up, mother!
She is alive! She is alive!
Come on! We're going!
Mother, hang on! Please don't...
leave me without you here!
You were so good, Boran Alp.
A valant was on the battlefield.
Thank Allah we're on the right side.
Thank you.
Ask permission first.
What do you want?
-I need you to help me.
-Shut up.
Shut up! You're a snake next
to another snake.
Why do you need my help?
Julia.
She will attack Hatuns. We
need to prevent this.
What trap are you trying to lure me into?
Did you make up for your previous
mistake...
so that I can believe your word now?
Boran, I saw my mistake and corrected it.
But if you don't come with me now,
very bad things will happen. Come on.
Are you on the right side?
I'm both on the right side...
and Osman Bey's side.
Come on.
Boran, what happened is
between you and me.
It's a secret, Boran.
If one of us gets in trouble, we'll help.
Don't you--
Only the one who receives
the secret knows the secret.
I know that I shouldn't tell
this to anyone.
Don't worry.
Come on, let's go.
Gündüz Bey is giving a feast
to celebrate his position.
Let's go.
Cevahir said there are other
shelters leading to the pass.
We'll wait here.
Alright.
Let's go.
I hesitate to say the grave situation...
but our Sultan's condition is not good.
Osman came as a traitor.
He did what was necessary and
intended to kill our Sultan.
He will be caught. Then, we'll ask
why he did this.
Osman's trial will not take place and he
will be killed on sight.
In the name of Allah.
In the name of the 99 names of
Allah who make everything...
happen with just one word and fill
our hearts with faith.
My Beys, as you know...
I aspire to be the Bey of Kayı Tribe.
A skillful Bey like you is suitable
to be the Bey of Kayı.
Alright, Beys. Those who will vote for
Gündüz Bey,
raise your hand.
Is that so?
So you prefer to be headless to
Gündüz Bey.
So you are saying being headless
is better than him.
Alright.
Then, you will not take anything from
the conquests of Gündüz Bey.
You will be deprived of a conqueror Bey.
Say it, Gündüz Bey.
Say what you couldn't say because
of your humility until this day.
The property of the enemy, Harmankaya
Castle belongs to Kayı now.
With the help of Vizier Alemşah...
it will be the property of Kayı Tribe.
It's wrong.
Harmankaya is your property now.
If you become the Bey of Kayı Tribe, it
will be the property of Kayı.
Then, the Beys will get their share.
They can sell their goods in
the markets of Harmankaya...
and graze their animals on its lands.
Many opportunities will be waiting
for them...
and they will be revived in their tribe.
I will repeat.
Those who will vote for
Gündüz Bey, raise your hand.
That's what they call trap.
Those bastards never stopped.
They wanted to kill firstly Sultan Mesud
and then, me.
My dagger is on the Sultan's back.
If they can't kill you, they will put the
blame of the Sultan's death on you.
It's me, Cevahir.
Come, my brother. It's up to
you from now on.
We have big trouble.
Get us out of the palace.
I know your trouble, my brother.
Cevahir!
You used me and tried
to kill the Sultan.
You made me a part of your treachery.
I will make you surrender.
What are you doing?
You were my brother, Turgut! How could
you do this?
Osman Bey, it's a black mark
on your name--
Belt up!
What do you know, Cevahir?
What do you know?
Are you trying to
tarnish my name?
Look at my eyes.
Do you see a traitor?
Sultan Mesud's aide...
tried to kill him in the first place.
And then, he tried to kill me.
He got what he deserved.
But I couldn't protect the Sultan.
It's a game of Geyhatu and Vizier
Alemşah.
You don't have a fault, Cevahir.
But those bastards want to ruin the
reputation of Osman Bey and Kayı Tribe.
Trust your brother Turgut.
What if it's a part of your plan?
Do I look like I'm planning something?
Tell me.
Put down your swords.
Why don't you talk, Kumral Abdal?
Tell us if she will be alright or not?
There's always hope.
But her wound is so deep.
So deep.
Kumral Abdal.
I made syrup.
May Allah give healing.
Thank you.
In the name of Allah.
It's because of me.
If she hadn't jumped in front of me...
Don't do this, Bala. You did nothing
wrong.
Also, Selcan Hatun is strong.
She will be alright.
Yes, she is strong. She is the mother of
Kayı Tribe.
She is strong.
My Allah, don't take our mother from us.
Amen.
Mother!
Mother?
-Mother?
-Mother Selcan?
Mother.
We're okay, mother.
Thanks to you, we're alright.
You'll be alright too.
Thank Allah.
It's good that there are good
and brave men like...
you in Konya, which is writhing...
in the clutches of traitors.
We'll get out of this palace.
Osman Bey, there's no possibility to leave
the palace under the cover of a merchant.
Everywhere is full of soldiers.
He is right. It is hard to leave
the palace in this situation.
Every hard thing has an easy way to do.
They wouldn't keep the
carcasses of these dogs...
we killed in the palace, would they?
The enemy was not able to harm us
thanks to two brave men.
May Allah bless them.
Who are those valants?
Their faces were covered, that's why we
have no idea, my Sheik.
We don't know but Allah does.
But with the one whose
heart is with us...
our hearts are one.
Whoever is a hypocrite, who wants
to kill us...
who sheds innocent people's
blood, we are...
far away from him until
the Day of Judgment.
But the Sword that wraps around
my daughters' neck is Nikola.
So, the Vizier holds its hilt.
Vizier Alemşah has given up the
right way for falsehood...
and changed guidance with perversion.
Hypocrites.
"Hypocrites...
are deaf...
dumb...
and blind.
They will not choose the right
way anymore."
The one who truly deserves the hide
is the one who never wants it.
Beys witnessed that...
Gündüz Bey waived his right in the past.
Although he was the biggest, he waived
his right, we are witness to this.
Yes, we are.
The order that I am talking about
is only possible with the conquest.
You will follow Gündüz Bey until
the enemy...
leave this land, Beys.
It's impossible for you to stop now.
But first, our tribes will be blessed with
the trophy from Harmankaya.
You are saying great things, Vizier...
but what about Osman Bey?
What will happen when he turns back?
Osman Bey is one of the
greatest valants of this land.
Sultan Mesud will forgive him...
when his anger is ceased.
I hope so.
Can I come in, my Bey?
Come.
There is news from Konya.
Osman Bey...
escaped when he was taken to Konya.
Also, he killed Sergeant İlgezdi and
many Seljuk soldiers.
One of his alps, Göktüğ was martyred
when they were running away.
Göktüğ.
The valant of Kayı, Göktüğ.
Göktuğ.
My brother.
Göktüğ!
You.. you...
What are you saying?
What do you mean by Göktüğ is dead?!
What are you talking about?!
Vizier.
Vizier...
my brother died because of you.
You brought death here.
And you will go by death.
Vizier.
Boran!
I said Boran!
What do you think you are doing by
glowering at the Vizier...
in the presence of your Bey?
It's enough, Boran.
Behave yourself.
Now...
get out of my sight!
Osman Bey.
You are doing wrong things...
while we hope you will be forgiven.
I knew Sergeant İlgezdi.
He was such a lion.
Osman is now on a road of no return.
Beys, as choosing Gündüz Bey as your
leader...
...you did what's best.
Give me some good news, Ferman.
My Bey...
...two men with their faces covered
failed all our moves.
But Selcen Hatun is heavily wounded.
Nos she is at the lodge.
But Selcen is heavily wounded.
So, all those men were beaten by two
face covered bandits...
...is that so?
Can't you just...
...succeed at one job when I am
not around...
...Ferman?
This is not over.
But first, I will see Geyhatu.
We will take care of the hatuns
eventually.
Commander Onat's order!
Not even a bird will fly around!
No one will leave Konya without
reporting!
Come on!
Wait!
I am saying not a bird will fly.
Where is this carriage going?
What does it carry?
It carries the men Osman killed.
Commander Onat's orders.
If you want to see a dead body,
uncover it.
It is fine. Take it!
Let's go!
Follow that carriage!
Mother!
Is she all right?
If anything happens to my mother...
...I will come for you.
Look what you have caused,
Gündüz Bey!
Look carefully.
How did it happen?
Tell me.
Who did this?
Who could?
Those you work with did it.
Whoever will benefit from our death
did it.
Julia.
The dog of that Nikola...
...whom you work with.
But not only Nikola is behind this.
You know whom we bother well,
Gündüz Bey.
Vizier Alemşah sent that dog after us.
Aren't you tired of blaming Alemşah for
everything that happens to you?
You know it better, Gündüz Bey.
Vizier and Nikola share a goal.
Mother.
I will not let them get away with this.
Did you just remember that I was your
mother?
You exiled me from my tribe.
Mother.
You didn't listen to your mother's words.
You didn't just lose me...
...you lost what your brother entrusted
to you.
You separated a mother from her child.
Tell me.
Who are you?
We now have full control over Kayı Tribe.
Their new Bey, Gündüz, listens to
everything I say.
Good.
Osman tried to kill the Sultan.
He is a traitor now.
Konya will be his grave.
They say Sultan is not in good condition.
What if he dies?
We will mourn, Alemşah.
We will mourn
His youngest son will become the Sultan.
The kid will listen to our orders.
Our moves have worked both in
orient and western.
Gündüz will take Harmankaya from Nikola.
This is the first move.
Later, İznik and every land around it...
...will be ours.
With the power I gathered from there...
...I will establish a huge army...
... consisting of Greeks, Turks,
and Mongols.
With this army...
...I will dethrone Argun Han, the ruler of
the Mongols.
I will sit on that throne.
Me.
You will sit on that throne.
Although they don't call me Sultan...
...I will be controlling
the whole Seljuk.
Osman is the only obstacle...
...for this.
Osman will die.
Where are you, Osman Bey?
Where are you?
Finally.
-Kosses!
-Finally!
Osman!
Where are you going?
So you are looking for me!
You are one of those looming over the
Seljuk like a nightmare!
Your end will be like your allies!
Now I will loom over you like a nightmare,
Osman!
Come here!
Come!
Osman, you first defeated Selman.
You escaped before they kill you there.
That dagger is for you!
You and your tribe will be remembered
as traitors when you die!
Allah will show what he sees to his
subjects!
Go, Osman Bey!
Our honor spreads from tongue to tongue!
The whole world knows Osman!
Don't worry!
Cevahir!
Brother!
Oh, my brother!
My brother!
A valiant dies...
...but his name remains.
You fought like a valiant, brother.
Go to out Allah with peace.
Brother!
I go to my Rabb's presence with
the comfort of...
...dying on the right path.
"I bear witness...
Allah is the greatest!
My end is here...
...but yours is not far either!
Allah!
Mashallah, Solgur Agha!
You screamed once and you put fear
in the heart of the oppressors.
You killed them like a hunter, mashallah.
They call me the lion hunter.
When I heard that dog call you Osman
I came.
Thank you, but you had to kill
dogs today...
...instead of lions.
Thank you.
If you ever have a problem in Konya, no
matter where I am, I will come.
Thank you.
Thank you too, Osman Bey.
Praise be!
Are you the son...
...Halime Hatun raised with a great
care?
If they knew you turned your back on
your brother...
...what would your mother, father say?
Have you ever thought about this?
Don't do this, mother.
I didn't turn my back on my brother.
You know, I always envied you.
What a good son Halime Hatun has raised,
I said.
He got his brother's back.
Cares for him like a mother...
...I said.
Don't say that, mother.
I am still on my brother's side.
Ask here.
Which side?
There is a story.
They were beating a man.
They were hitting his chest.
But the man was crying
''My back, my back!''.
Finally, they stopped and asked.
''We are hitting your chest...
...Why are you crying for your back?''
Do you know what he said?
He said, ''If my back was tough,
protected...
...you wouldn't be able to hit my chest.''
A brother protects your back.
Go, sit on your throne.
Come on.
Bless your right to me, mother.
I don't want to see you anymore.
Go.
I have no right on you as a mother.
But know that...
...I will pray as your aunt until my
last breath...
...for you to see what is right.
My Sheik.
My Sheik, my heart is burning.
My heart is burning, my Sheik.
Would I ever do this if I knew this
would happen?
If you knew and you did, you would be
an oppressor.
You are one of the heedless for
doing it unknowingly.
For the sake of my tribe...
...for the sake of all of us!
I wanted to expel the hatuns not to shed
blood.
They would of course return when I
set an order, my Sheik.
I didn't want this to happen.
A Muslim should be wise.
He should always be cautious, Gündüz Bey.
Do you know the infidels who built
Mescid-i Dırar?
Their aim was to cause discord
among believers...
...and to help those who were
hostile to Allah...
...and the Prophet.
They wanted to paint the nest of betrayal
and sin...
...as Allah's home.
But nothing is a secret to our Allah.
He is the one hearing and seeing all.
He informed the prophet of their intention
in Surah At-Tawba.
It was forbidden to come to
the presence of Allah...
...in the evil house,
that so-called mosque.
The Prophet of Allah immediately
destroyed that nest of discord.
The verses of Allah and the Sunnah
of His Prophet are obvious.
Do you think those hypocrites who built
Mescid-i Dırar...
...are today doing nothing, Gündüz Bey?
They don't.
But the heedless prostrate themselves
in the taverns...
...and palaces of the hypocrites today.
They don't destroy them Gündüz Bey.
We are always against those hypocrites,
my Sheik.
But, I see that...
...you blame Alemşah for every evil too.
I vouch for his intentions, my Sheik.
He thinks for the sake of the Turks.
Vizier Alemşah...
...sealed your eyes, your ears and
your heart with evil so badly that...
...you haven't been able to wake up for
so long.
The end of those who persist in
heedlessness is hypocrisy.
Obviously, my word means nothing to you.
Gündüz Bey...
...if you ever wish to wake up...
...be a disciple of your conscience,
a guide to your soul.
Everything is clear and obvious.
Vizier Alemşah and Geyhatu are working
together.
That is clear.
But, what will we do now?
What to do is certain.
Sultan Mesud also needs to see they
work together.
We do.
But they are so good at deceiving.
Do we know...
...if Sultan Mesid is alive or dead?
I hope he is alive.
If he dies...
...all this will get even worse.
Let's pray he lives.
Otherwise seems terrible.
I've spent so much time with Sultan Mesud.
He is a strong man.
He is made of steel.
-He will recover.
-I hope.
Sultan will recover for sure but...
...how are we going to heal these
wounds, Osman?
They took your tribe.
They took my castle.
Both of our states know us as traitors.
Tell me, what are we going to do now?
Understanding what I am about to
say...
...will be hard for you, Kosses.
Is the property ours to be sad when
we lose it?
The property belongs only to Allah.
My tribe is a vehicle for me.
I burn with love to glorify it.
This is my only aim.
Let them know us how they want to.
Our intention is pure, our way is
the right way.
Thank you.
So your tribe is not liable to you,
you are liable to your tribe?
Do you share his opinion, Turgut?
If we had şeft everything behind and
spent the night in this cave...
...sure we share the same opinion.
But my only worry is...
...Mari.
Mari is a very strong girl.
He learned how to fight from his brother.
Thank you.
Also, Kayı's hatuns are with her.
They will protect each other, right,
Osman Bey?
They will protect each other.
And we will protect each other.
May my Allah grant us fighting for
the same cause together.
Amen.
After I get my castle, I will continue
to my way, Osman Bey.
You know, my enmity with you goes back
a long time.
Fate opens such doors that...
...it is not known who will be friends
with whom...
...and who will be enemies.
If you are here with me now...
...there sure is a reason.
My Sultan!
Thank goodness!
Who did this to me?
Osman, my Sultan.
Osman!
Osman has escaped the palace.
He is searched everywhere.
It is said that he left Konya.
Sultan is still alive.
Osman!
You got away again huh?
I will get your head, for sure.
Gündüz Bey, the Bey of Kayı is here!
Let him in!
Welcome, Gündüz Bey.
I wish to speak with you alone.
Who did this treacherous attack...
...on the hatuns...
...Vizier Alemşah?
I've heard.
I sent soldiers there as soon as I heard.
It is said that Julia had done it.
It is obvious that this is Nikola's doing.
Slime bag!
He is only strong enough
to mess with hatuns.
Nikola huh?
He shed the blood of Mother Selcan huh!?
As soon as he leaves that castle...
...I know exactly what to do to him.
Vizier Alam Shah,...
...I will rally the entire Turkmen.
There is no need for that, Güzdüz Bey.
Tomorrow, the ones that take
Harmankaya will pay a heavy price.
Tonight, I will head to where Nikola is.
I will divert him.
And you, by morning, will conquer
Harmankaya with you alps.
But anything can be expected from Nikola.
Take Turkmen Beys with you as well...
...so that they can't stand in your way.
Have them earn all that loot.
Harmankaya will be the property
of Kayı, from now onward.
Thank Allah!
I wouldn't want to give
you such bad news...
...when you're in a pleasant state, but...
...we just got word from Konya...
...Osman has arrived at Konya...
...and met with Sultan.
Thank goodness!
Thank you, Allah!
He stabbed Sultan in the back.
He tried to kill him.
And then escaped.
What?
Your brother has no chance
to redeem himself anymore.
If he ever falls into my hands...
...don't you dare standing in my way.
I will take his life the moment I see him.
Your duty is to be a
worthy bey to your tribe.
You have to qualify for being a bey.
Osman...
...find him and get him
to me alive and well.
Sultan Mesut your excellence,
Osman tried to kill you.
He killed commander Tebugay and escaped.
We're looking for Osman, when
we find him we will kill him.
Osman will not die!
I will personally ask him...
...the things he has done.
Find him and get him here.
Osman will die.
And what's more is, he himself
will come to his own death.
How is Selcan Hatun?
Now well, my Vizier.
Her wound is too deep.
What will Osman do when her
mother is on her deathbed, Konur?
Naturally, he'll go to visit his mother.
Do not avert your eyes from the monastery.
I'm at your command, my vizier.
Dear Allah the greatest,...
I'm never afraid of
the trap of the cruel...
...or the mischief of the hypocrite.
I always pray to you and...
...always trust your plan.
Dear Allah,...
...dear Allah,...
...allow me and my generation to spread...
...the holy word to the entire world.
Help me to stand still on the path...
...of spreading your words, dear Allah!
The merciful,...
...the gracious Allah...
...protect us from all the small or big...
...misdeeds standing in the way of...
...spreading Islam to the whole world.
Dear Allah,...
...If I'm in this trouble now, it's the...
...the dream of this blessed government
that got me into this trouble.
Dear Allah...
...allow me to honorable redeem myself...
...from all the smears thrown on me.
Grace me with brothers of
the same objective, dear Allah!
So that, I can spread your name,...
...the belief of Islam to the whole world.
Dear Allah,...
...I got one life and I sacrifice it
for your path, dear Allah!
You, you are the wisest.
Give me strength to...
...overcome these struggles.
Give me strength to make this blessed...
...government dominate the entire world.
Amen, Dear Allah!
Amen!
How did you handle this, Bamsı Bey?
You buried your brothers, like me.
Give me advice,...
...the dual weapons of Bamsı Bey.
Bamsı Bey suffered all the pain I have.
You witnessed all of it.
How did he handle it?
Tell me!
Were you the ones that gave him strength?
Give it to me as well!
Tell me!
What am I going to do, now?
One of my brothers have gotten martyred.
The other has lost his
mind more than I have.
What am I going to do now?
What am I supposed to do?
I am supposed to be virtuous...
...just like Bamsı Bey.
I am supposed to kill them
all with these weapons!
I promise!
I will butcher them all...
...with these weapons!
Brother!
Now, I understand your reputation.
We're in a terrible state...
...and you vow to get revenge.
You are out of your mind.
It's not about using weapons, brother.
It's about heart.
It's about believing.
It is not enough...
...to lead men.
You have to make them believe it.
My bey made us believe it.
My bey gave us courage.
What about you?
I came all the way from Caucaus.
I followed Osman Bey.
I am one of the believers, brother.
If you lost a brother,...
...you've gained one, know that.
Praise be, my brothers!
Praise be!
İNEGÖL CASTLE
Vizier Alam Shah!
I have important news, Nikola.
When do you ever give unimportant news?
We tricked Osman so well in Konya.
He is now a traitor who
intended to kill Sultan Mesut.
How did that happen?
That is my secret.
We now got Osman out of our way, forever?
Right? Osman no longer has a head...
...upon his body, right?
Not yet.
Osman somehow found a
way to escape from the palace.
To hell with him! How could this happen?
How could you let him slip away from your
hands when you managed to pin such a...
...major crime on him?
This is such a disappointment,
Vizier Alam Shah!
Finding Kosses who we thought was in
Constantinople, helping Osman in Konya...
...was a greater disappointment, Nikola.
You tell me,...
...what was he doing there?
I should have killed Kosses
before he got to Constantinople!
It is what it is, Nikola.
No point in whining now.
But you should not hide your failures...
...like how you don't hide your victories.
You don't hide them so that we know...
...exactly what we're dealing with.
And you do not need to
worry about Osman either...
...Seljuk soldiers will
find him sooner or later.
His head will not stay
on his body for long.
Then, I promise that,...
...I will find Kosses myself
and kill him with my hands.
I promise!
I trust you, Nikola.
Do what you say.
The samples of the goods that we will
bring to the bazaar will come here...
...by tomorrow morning. I will personally
show them to you, by early in the morning.
That's why...
...tonight, I am a guest
at your castle, Nikola.
I would be honored.
Where is Osman?
Tell my Osman...
...that your mother does
gives her blessings to you.
Always be one on the path for Osman's...
...dream for the government.
If Allah permits, you will
see those days together.
Don't say that, mother! If Allah
permits, we will all see it together.
It's destiny my girl.
I was destined to see him become a bey...
...but I guess I am not destined to
see him form his own government.
It all will happen, aunt.
Those days will happen
as well if Allah permits.
My Osman dreams about the sacred...
...government, right?
Know that your children...
...will be the expression
of Osman's dream.
It is your, the mothers' duty to teach...
...that to your children.
Mothers are the chasteners of the tent...
...they are the rearers of it.
From a family, a tribe grows,...
...from a tribe, a government grows.
The government that my Osman will
establish will be stronger with...
...your merciful, noble hands.
My Orhan...
...and my Korhan...
...will stand by their
brother, no matter what.
I know that you will raise your
children to...
...serve for their government.
What is it that is
motherless in the universe?
Let the government be motherless.
Eventually,...
...the government my
Osman will establish...
...will become better with
you two valiant mothers.
Thank Allah!
I want everything to be perfect, Erdoğdu!
Did you hear me?
Seeing that infidel Nikola who hurt my
mother and my sisters...
...sitting on the Harmankaya throne
makes me boil over.
Harmankaya will belong to Kayı.
Alps can't wait for conquest, my bey.
We are ready.
With Allah's permission,
we will conquer Harmankaya.
That we will.
We will.
Come on, go be with your alps.
Yes, my bey.
Osman has gotten himself...
...in a lot of trouble, Ayşe.
They say that he tried to kill the Sultan.
Fortunately, Sultan did not die.
It's all slander, my bey.
Osman Bey would
never do such a thing.
Osman has done all kinds of things lately.
All kinds of things.
What they say even makes
me have a suspicion.
He is the one who made everything worse...
...by escaping and not surrendering
when he should have.
Oh, my brother.
I wish you had listened to me.
Gündüz.
They have tricked Osman Bey.
Osman Bey would never draw
his weapon on Sultan Mesut.
I don't know, Ayşe.
I don't know.
Nothing is clear.
However,...
...nobody will know of this crime
that's been pinned on Osman.
Don't you dare!
If Seljuk does not impound our tribe
after everything, Osman has done...
...it is because of Alam Shah.
But,...
...I will do whatever I can for our tribe.
Kayı Tribe will be prosperous!
Kayı Oba will be peaceful!
To do that, I will make Harmankaya
belong to Kayı.
Boran,
Osman Bey has escaped alive.
Thank you, Allah.
Don't be so happy yet.
Vizier is up to some treacherous games.
He knows Osman Bey will visit Selcan
Hatun one way or another.
He requests a title deed for the monastery
That weasel!
The pain he has caused the games
he has played weren't enough...
...he is now up to more.
We should inform Osman Bey of this.
I'll do it. I'll do it.
Where is my bey now?
He is on his way here from Konya.
May Allah bless you!
The places we hide in
the forest are apparent.
I know where to find my bey.
Boran,...
...don't tell anyone that
the news came from me.
This is our secret.
May Allah bless you!
Amen!
My valiant,...
...Göktuğ.
Brother.
Brother!
My martyr.
Let Allah bring us together
again in heaven.
I promise,...
...that I will get vengeance for you
and for all of our martyrs.
Brother,...
...you believed Allah's
word with all your heart.
My brave brother.
We are content with you.
Let Allah be content as well.
Göktuğ,
My brother.
I guess it's my destiny
to fight without you.
It will be difficult, Göktuğ.
Your absence breaks my heart brother.
We will get revenge for brother Göktuğ.
Don't worry about it, brother.
We will.
We won't break.
Göktuğ was the friend
we always wanted to have.
We're here, Cerkutay.
We're here.
Turgut.
Yes, OsmanBey.
Kosses,
Go to Yirce with alps.
We'll meet there.
We'll go but what about you?
It's very dangerous, Osman Bey.
They're looking for you everywhere.
My way is to salvation.
Do not worry.
May Allah bless you!
You've never seen anything
like it in this soil, Nikola.
I really haven't
Very sharp.
We'll earn a lot in this bazaar.
But, these are the most important.
HARMANKAYA CASTLE
Why did you throng here
with a crowd, Gündüz Bey?
Is there something we do not know?
We did not come for a visit.
We're here to take the castle.
Soldiers!
Do you think I don't know
of your cunningness?
So, Nikola gathered
the castle with soldiers?
Come on, Valiants!
Come on, Valiants! Show no mercy!
Salam aleikum!
Aleikum salam!
We heard that Geyhatu has come back.
His goal is to...
...cost Argun Khan the throne.
He wants to have power in this soil.
That's true.
He is in preparation for a
rebellion against Argun Khan
He aims to conquer the entire land...
...and create a gigantic army.
Lords, Turkmen Beys, he'll
take them all along with him.
Vizier Alam Shah is working with him.
He wants to control Seljuk.
That way he'll grow his army even bigger.
Unless you prevent that from
happening of course.
The breath I take is for that.
That is the only thing
that beats my heart.
It is the dream of a government
that keeps me standing.
Tell us then,...
...what are you going to do now?
Politics.
If they want to play a game...
...if they want to break the rules...
...if they try to set up an order
that we say is detrimental...
...then, I will destroy them.
Vizier Alam Shah...
...created a unit.
I will destroy it.
If the goal of Geyhatu and
Vizier Alam Shah is to...
...take down the Lords and gain power...
...I will prevent that from happening.
You said well, but...
...tell us how you're going
to do that Osman Bey.
Lord Kosses,...
...has been with me for a while.
Now I'm going to get the weakest link...
...on my side.
İnegöl Lord, Aya Nikola.
If my brother and my beys
turn their backs on me...
...then, I'll confront them...
...with soldiers of lords.
I will not leave these
lands, these soils...
...to Geyhatu's and Vizier Alam Shah's
treacherous ambitions.
Never.
Alam Shah, Gündüz Bey have
started to move already.
They have gone to take Harmankaya.
Whereas you are in front of us.
You're too late, Osman Bey.
I know, may Allah bless you!
Vizier Alam Shah's aim is not to...
...strenghten the lords.
It is to destroy them.
That's why I had informed Nikola before.
He probably took precautions.
Do you have faith that Nikola
can stop this, Osman Bey?
Never.
But,...
...I have decided who to side with...
...when I'm on the edges.
I showed him the way.
He'll be with us too.
Until the government, we
planted the seeds for...
...is established.
Then, all the tyrants will pay.
Ertuğrul Bey.
May he rest in peace.
Amen.
He was right to make you a bey.
Let's get to the main point.
Turkmen tribes are revolting.
To ease the rebellion,
Argun Khan is sending...
...an army of twenty thousand
men to Geyhatun's commands.
He'll be even more powerful with them.
Rebellion is an excuse.
These edges are not his concern.
The entire land is.
Hurry up, Osman Bey.
On the verge of handling one trouble
the other is on the way.
The destiny of the Turk is in your hand.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey!
We have no doubt, but we'd like to know...
...where are you heading, Osman Bey?
To Kızıl Elma.
No power, no struggle
can stand in our way.
We're not alone on this path.
Even if we're not in our tribe...
...our tribe works like a sharp weapon...
...you beat it in heat.
Godspeed!
May I Allah bless you, Osman Bey!
May Allah help you!
- Allah is eternal!
- Allah is right!
Allah is eternal!
Our bey wants it, we do it!
He goes through all kinds of trouble
and still has a lust for conquest.
You have come here
believing as well brothers!
These weapons will not
enter the holsters of alps dry.
They'll be soaked with
the blood of tyrants.
- We believe it!
We beat weapons today,...
...walls tomorrow.
If Allah permits, conquest is near.
- If Allah permits!
Allah is the greatest!
Sir, Gündüz Bey, and his men have
attacked the Castle of Harmankaya.
There were a lot of them.
We have lost the castle, sir.
Incompetents! Fools!
Arguz!
Every time I asked you, you sad
" The castle is safe sir"...
...the castle you call safe
is now in the hands of Kayı!
Don't act hotheaded, Nikola.
You distracted me!
You gave my castle to Gündüz
by distracting me, Vizier!
Isn't that right?
You made a mistake, a very big mistake!
A very big mistake!
Mongols!
Geyhatu is approaching!
Open the gate!
Thank Allah, Harmankaya
now belongs to Kayı!
- Thank Allah!
Thank Allah for gracing
us with this conquest!
- Thank Allah!
I have to say that Vizier Alam Shah has
been very contributary for this conquest.
He wanted the best for the...
...Turkmen Tribes and the Kayı Tribe...
...and conduced with this conquest.
Vizier and I have the same goal in mind.
We want Turkmens to live
prosperously in the entire world.
- Amen!
On this mission, we won't shy away from...
...drawing our weapons or endangering
our own lives so help us, Allah!
May Allah bless your conquest, Gündüz Bey!
I was against you being a bey but,
you have surprised me...
...and it's a good thing
you did, Gündüz Bey.
- May you live long!
May Allah bless you! All of
you may live long as well!
Do not forget,...
...once we're all together...
...these types of conquests will not stop!
- Thank Allah!
Erdoğdu,...
...hand out the loots equally.
Yes, my bey!
May Allah bless you, my bey!
Thank you, Gündüz Bey!
Thank you, my bey!
May Allah bless you, my bey!
Why don't we kill you, Nikola?
Why don't you kill me, Geyhatu?
Because you're a man whose shadow
is bigger than himself.
We need your shadow.
There is a Mongolian army
in your yard, Nikola.
Thanks to you, Vizier Alam Shah!
Thanks to you!
You don't have your lord
friends to help you neither.
We sent them packing, together.
Don't be blind like Osman.
Don't be blind so that
you won't live the same fate.
You're a wise man, Nikola.
Harmankaya,...
...is just a part of one
of our grand desires.
What are your grand desires?
Calm your nerves, Nikola!
Or I'll build a castle made of
y our and your soldiers' skulls.
Kayı Tribe now belongs to us.
Gündüz is in the palm of our hands, now.
Be sure that, that tribe is more
valuable than the castle.
Alright, but what do you
want from me and my castle?
Our enemies are the same.
The prize will be the same as well.
Kayı is ours.
Seljuk will be ours as well!
And you will form a government here.
Osman is a living dead...
...lords are banished.
Nobody is standing our way.
Harmankaya is just a little price we paid.
I'm going to make you a government, here.
I overthrow and build governments.
What is your offer, Geyhatu?
Don't you want to resurrect the...
...holy Roman Empire
on these lands, Nikola?
I would love to.
If you serve our interests
and be loyal to us...
...Geyhatu will make all
of that happen for you.
But Osman has to die as soon as possible.
He'll go to visit his mother Selcan Hatun.
Once Osman dies...
...we'll talk about the rest later.
Soldiers!
Mother Selcan,...
...Kayı's valiant mother...
...I will make them pay for what
they have done to her!
We will, brother.
We will if Allah permits.
May Allah help us to get revenge
on the tyrants for the oppressed.
Amen!
No crime will be without
punishment, Turgut.
I swear, whoever caused
all this suffering...
...will suffer themselves.
May Allah bless you, Kosses!
Brother, my bey is coming.
- Boran,
- My bey,
Brother,
Brother.
My bey.
I've got important news, my bey.
Tell me about it.
My bey, Gündüz Bey...
What is up with Gündüz Bey?
He banished the hatuns alongside with...
...the blacksmith from the tribe.
Brother.
Brother!
My bey,
They got ambushed on the way.
What?
What are you saying?
What are you saying, Boran?
Orhan, my mother, Malhun
Bala, how are they?
Tell me!
Orhan is at the tribe, my bey.
Hatuns are well too.
However, Selcan Mother...
Mother.
My Bey, traitor vizier attacked the
Hatuns.
Selcan Mother is hurt.
She's in the lodge now.
Kumral Abdal is with her.
Mother... Is she okay?
Is she alive? Tell me.
I don't hide things from you, my Bey.
She is alive.
However, her wound...
is deep, my Bey.
Vizier... Vizier Alemşah...
Find a grave for yourself.
- Come on! Let's go to mother.
- Stop, my Bey.
Vizier knows you're going to the lodge.
He's ready.
If you go to the lodge,
you'll fall into his trap.
I won't let Vizier and his men harm us.
Boran.
We will go to my mother's.
Go to Edebalı.
He should tell all dervishes around.
He should invite them to Söğüt.
And we will go to Selcan Mother to Söğüt.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on.
It's because of me.
Don't say that, I saved my child.
I saved my children.
She has fever.
I should tell Kumral Abdal.
Come on, Zehra.
Mother.
No.
Mother. You're leaving me.
Don't.
Mother! No! Mother!
Mother! Mother!
Mother! Selcan Mother!
Welcome.
We've been waiting for you.
Thank Allah you're here.
My Sheikh will be happy to see you.
Watch them. I'll let Vizier know.
Your command.
We placed our soldiers everywhere, sir.
However, no one saw Osman.
He won't come, obviously.
Osman will come, Ferman.
He will want to see her
before his Selcan Mother dies.
Watch them carefully.
I don't want any mistakes.
- Can I come in, my Vizier?
- Come in.
Some people dressed as dervishes came.
They're in the lodge. Obviously, they
are Osman and his Alps.
Osman won't come
out of Söğüt today.
Söğüt will be his grave.
Come on let's visit Edebalı.
Look everywhere! Find Osman!
Look everywhere!
"And they argue with Us—forgetting
they were created—
...saying, “Who will give life to
decayed bones?...
...Say, ˹O Prophet,˺ “They will be revived by the One Who produced them the first time...
He has ˹perfect˺ knowledge of every
created being." -Surah Ya-Sin
Where's Osman, Edebalı?
Where did you hide him?
"Allah Almighty speaks the truth."
Show some respect!
You can't show up to a funeral like that!
Stop, Vizier Alemşah!
Find traitor Osman.
Look everywhere!
Even if he's lost, find him.
- Stop!
- Get out of my way, dervish.
You have no mercy to alive, don't you
have respect for the dead?
It's inconsiderate of you to do that.
It's inconsiderate of you to
help a traitor and hide him.
Where are you going?
Osman is here. I know.
What are you saying? We
have a dead! Don't you see?
We'll search the room.
Do it!
What are you doing? Don't you see
that we have a funeral?
It's a woman.
You can't come in here.
Get out.
You too, Celali. Don't you hear them?
Don't you have respect for the dead?
Konur, choose your side.
You are being too much.
You are being disrespectful.
I side with the right ones.
Stop what you're doing or I kill you.
I pretend to not hear that.
Let the soldiers do their job.
Osman is a traitor.
Search the room.
Don't you have a heart?
Forgive us.
Sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Bring them.
Ever since you came, you've
been slandering people.
You are being very cruel...
and our Allah won't forgive that.
You're leading yourself to
hell because of that.
Stop talking about hell when
you are protecting a traitor.
You are the one who are going to hell.
You come here without respect and talk.
You are being disrespectful, you
don't know what pain is.
However, I see that dead people
are more alive than you.
They are less decayed.
Your soul is decayed and you don't
know that.
I will cut your tongues and cut
Osman's head.
Don't worry.
You'll see what decaying is then.
Bring them.
Open their faces.
Vizier Alemşah...
Whoever has evil in their hearts...
will be punished afterlife.
You will too.
My Allah won't always punish
people afterlife, may punish you alive.
You will be punished by valiants.
Your punishment will be
hard for you, Vizier Alemşah.
Ensheathe the swords.
Their punishments will be big...
when the time comes.
Oh.
I thought that only our cities and castles
are full of bridges and secret passages.
My Bey.
Under the Söğüt is dangerous.
We don't know what we need
and when we need.
This leads us to Vizier's death.
Alps. Listen to me carefully.
Kosses, catch the soldiers
you see and hide yourselves.
This night will become
Vizier's last night.
However, don't kill anyone
else except for him.
- Understand?
- Yes.
Come on.
Come, Vizier Alemşah.
Come and...
let justice be done!
When he hears that my mother is dead...
he'll think that I will go to the funeral.
Mother.
My Osman. You came.
- I did, mother.
- Thank Allah.
- I came, mother.
Kumra Abdal, how's she?
Thank Allah, she's fine. Her wound is...
not bad. She needs to rest.
My mother is a powerful Hatun.
She will be better.
However, only we will know that.
Bala, stay with her.
Malhun, you stay here too.
Tell everyone that my mother is dead.
Vizier will think she's dead.
He will die soon or later.
Look everywhere!
My Bey, how will you get out of here?
Don't worry, my Alps planned everything.
Listen to me carefully now.
That's why he'll set a
trap in the graveyard.
And he won't have any soldiers in Söğüt...
that will protect him from me.
I'll get you, Vizier Alemşah.
I will kill you here.
If Osman is not here now, he will come to
the graveyard anyway. (cemetery)
Ferman, let Geyhatu know.
Tell him Osman will come.
Celali and Konur, go to the graveyard.
Place a man everywhere. Osman
won't go out of the graveyard.
Don't worry.
We will bury Osman in his own grave.
Come, Osman.
I will bury you with
your loved one Selcan Mother.
Come, Vizier.
Osman.
Yes, Osman.
You thought your sneaky plans would
go on, right, Vizier Alemşah?
I didn't have a sword, Osman.
You will be known as a traitor
when you kill me.
Soldiers!
You tried to make me a Sultan killer.
Now, do you want me to not kill you?
Heathens are on the bottom of the fire.
You can't find anyone who will save them.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com